Stephen Hess Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
Stephen Hess Papers 1961-2016
MSS83739
Hess, Stephen
35,350 items
101 containers
40.4 linear feet
426 digital files (118.96GB)
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Political scientist and author. Interviews, surveys, research material, digital video files, correspondence, memoranda, and other material relating to Hess's professional life, including his work as a Brookings Institution fellow and George Washington University faculty member, as well as his tenure as Richard M. Nixon's Deputy Assistant to the President for Urban Affairs.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Ehrlichman, John.; Hess, Stephen.; Hess, Stephen. Government/press connection: press officers and their offices. 1984.; Hess, Stephen. International news & foreign correspondents. 1996.; Hess, Stephen. Live from Capitol Hill!: studies of Congress and the media. 1991.; Hess, Stephen. Through their eyes: foreign correspondents in the United States. 2005.; Moynihan, Daniel P. (Daniel Patrick), 1927-2003.; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994.
Organizations
Brookings Institution.; George Washington University--Faculty.; George Washington University. School of Media and Public Affairs.; United States. Congress--Reporters and reporting.; United States. Deputy Assistant to the President for Urban Affairs.; United States. White House Office.; White House Conference on Children (1971: Washington, D.C.); White House Conference on Children and Youth (1969: Washington, D.C.); White House Conference on Children and Youth (1970: Washington, D.C.); White House Conference on Youth (1971: Estes Park, Colo.); White House Urban Affairs Council.
Subjects
Children--United States.; Cities and towns--United States.; Elections--United States.; Foreign correspondents--United States.; Foreign news.; Government and the press--United States.; Journalism.; Journalists--Washington (D.C.); Local mass media--United States.; Political science.; Presidents--United States--Election.; Press and politics--United States.; Press secretaries--United States.; Reporters and reporting--United States.; Reporters and reporting--Washington (D.C.); Television broadcasting of news--United States.; Urban policy--United States.; Youth--United States.
Places
United States--Politics and government.; United States--Social conditions.; United States--Social policy.
Occupations
Authors.; Political scientists.
Provenance
The papers of Stephen Hess, political scientist and author, were deposited in the Library of Congress by Hess in 1996 and 2012. Additional material was given by him in 2017, and the deposits were converted to a gift in 2017.
Transfers
Multiple items have been transferred to the Motion Picture, Broadcasting, and Recorded Sound Division, where they are identified as part of the Stephen Hess Papers.
Access and Restrictions
The papers of Stephen Hess are open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Manuscript Reading Room prior to visiting. Many collections are stored off-site and advance notice is needed to retrieve these items for research use.
Digital Format
Digital files were received as part of the papers of Stephen Hess. Reference copies were created from the original digital media. Advanced notice is required for access to digital content; consult reference staff in the Manuscript Division for more information.
Biographical Note
Date Event
1933, 20 Apr. Born, New York, N.Y.
1953 Graduated, Johns Hopkins University, Baltimore, Md.
1959 1961 Special Assistant in the White House Office
1969 Deputy Assistant to the President for Urban Affairs
1969 1971 National Chairman of the White House Conference on Children and Youth
1972 Joined the Brookings Institution, Washington, D.C.
1974 United States representative to the Unesco General Conference
1976 United States representative to the United Nations General Assembly
1979 1982 Fellow of Government, Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
1984 Published The Government/Press Connection: Press Officers and Their Offices. Washington, D.C.: Brookings Institution
1991 Published Live From Capitol Hill!: Studies of Congress and the Media. Washington, D.C.: Brookings Institution
1996 Published International News & Foreign Correspondents. Washington, D.C.: Brookings Institution
2004 2009 Distinguished research professor of media and public affairs, the George Washington University, Washington, D.C.
2005 Published Through Their Eyes: Foreign Correspondents in the United States. Washington, D.C.: Brookings Institution Press
2012 Published Whatever Happened to the Washington Reporters: 1978-2012. Washington, D.C.: Brookings Institution Press
Scope and Content Note
The papers of Stephen Hess (1933- ) span the years 1961 to 2016. The papers are in English and are organized into the following three series: Brookings Institution, George Washington University School of Media and Public Affairs Interviews, and White House Files.
Brookings Institution files consist of research material for various projects and books authored by Hess while a Brookings Institution fellow. Hess's research pursuits chiefly concern foreign correspondents in the United States and Washington, D.C. area reporters. The material includes the results of surveys of foreign correspondents conducted in 1982, 1992, and 1999. There are also transcripts, responses, and results of surveys and interviews with reporters conducted in 1978, from 1987 to 1989, and from 2005 to 2006. Other research materials concern the impact of local television news, presidential campaigns and election coverage, and congressional press secretaries. There are also notes, drafts, and other research material for the following books: The Government/Press Connection: Press Officers and Their Offices, Live From Capitol Hill!: Studies of Congress and the Media, International News & Foreign Correspondents, and Through Their Eyes: Foreign Correspondents in the United States.
The George Washington University School of Media and Public Affairs Interviews consist of forty-four digital video interviews of journalists and authors conducted for Stephen Hess's course on career patterns in journalism from 2006 to 2009. The interviews were conducted by Hess in a studio or classroom with an audience present. Hess asked participants to speak about their professional lives, which generally concerned government and politics. Interviews usually included a question-and-answer session with students and audience members. Some files contain video playback errors, such as dropouts, interference, static or color shifting, and audio errors, such as pops, clicks or clipping. Files are as they were received from the donor.
White House Files consist chiefly of memoranda and correspondence with White House officials, cabinet secretaries and undersecretaries, and members of Congress during Stephen Hess's tenure in the Nixon administration from 1969 to 1971. As Deputy Assistant to the President for Urban Affairs and subsequently chairman of the White House Conference on Children and Youth, Hess worked closely with Daniel P. Moynihan and John Ehrlichman. The material is mostly arranged in alphabetical, chronological, personal, and subject files. There are also files related to Hess's work with various groups, organizations, government agencies, and commissions, including the White House Urban Affairs Council. Personal files include material concerning a 1969 trip to Japan, Hong Kong, and Singapore.
Arrangement of the Papers
This collection is arranged in three series:
Brookings Institution, 1961-2016
George Washington University School of Media and Public Affairs Interviews, 2006-2009
White House Files, 1967-1971, 2009
Container List
- Brookings Institution, 1961-2016 (Box 1-70)
  Reporter interviews, surveys, and research material chiefly, concerning foreign correspondents and news media coverage of government and politics in the United States.
  Arranged alphabetically by name, title, or topic.
  - Brookings/Harvard forum: "Press Coverage and the War on Terrorism," 2001-2002, (7 folders) (Box 1)
  - Covering wars, 1993, (4 folders) (Box 2)
  - Debate files
    - Presidential debates, 1976-1996, (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Gallup poll data, 1984-1992 (Box 2)
    - Media coverage, 1987-1995 (Box 3)
    - Format and scheduling, 1995 (Box 3)
    - Conclusions and recommendations, 1979-1994 (Box 3)
    - Miscellany, 1992-1993 (Box 3)
  - "The Decline and Fall of Congressional News," 1993, (6 folders) (Box 3)
  - Foreign correspondents material
    - Articles, 1993, (4 folders) (Box 4)
    - Congressional Directory foreign press corps tally digital files, 2003-2005, mss83739_163_047
    - Editor and Publisher's International Yearbook foreign correspondents tally, 1964-2000 (Box 4)
    - Editor and Publisher's International Yearbook foreign correspondents tally digital files, 2003, mss83739_163_048
    - Foreign Press Association tally, 1961-2003 (Box 4)
    - Foreign reporting practices, 1994, (3 folders) (Box 5)
    - International newspaper bylines, 1982, (4 folders) (Box 5)
    - Interviews, 1977-2002, (4 folders) (Box 6)
    - Inventory, 1985, (3 folders) (Box 6)
    - Lists and records, 1992, (5 folders) (Box 7)
    - Surveys
      - 1982, (3 folders) (Box 7)
      - 1992
        - "A" responses (Box 8)
        - "B" responses, (3 folders) (Box 8)
        - "C" responses, (2 folders) (Box 8)
        - "D" responses (Box 9)
        - "E" responses (Box 9)
        - "F" responses (Box 9)
        - "G" responses, (2 folders) (Box 9)
        - "H" responses, (2 folders) (Box 9)
        - "I" responses (Box 10)
        - "J" responses (Box 10)
        - "K" responses, (2 folders) (Box 10)
        - "L" responses, (2 folders) (Box 10)
        - "M" responses, (3 folders) (Box 10)
        - "N" responses (Box 11)
        - "O" responses (Box 11)
        - "P-Q" responses (Box 11)
        - "R" responses, (2 folders) (Box 11)
        - "S" responses, (2 folders) (Box 11)
        - "T" responses (Box 12)
        - "U" responses (Box 12)
        - "V" responses (Box 12)
        - "W" responses (Box 12)
        - "Y-Z" responses (Box 12)
        - Crosstabulation by country, (4 folders) (Box 12)
        - General run without "NA's" (Box 13)
        - Responses not coded (Box 13)
      - 1999
        - 1-30 responses (Box 13)
        - 31-63 responses (Box 13)
        - 64-99 responses (Box 13)
        - 100-139 responses (Box 13)
        - 140-176 responses (Box 13)
        - 177-199 responses (Box 14)
        - 200-234 responses (Box 14)
        - 235-264 responses (Box 14)
        - 265-299 responses (Box 14)
        - 300-339 responses (Box 14)
        - 340-374 responses (Box 14)
        - 375-411 responses (Box 15)
        - 412-441 responses (Box 15)
        - Coding sheet, (5 folders) (Box 15)
        - Coding sheet, (3 folders) (Box 16)
        - Correspondents and interviews by country (Box 16)
        - Data analysis, (3 folders) (Box 16)
        - Final report, (2 folders) (Box 17)
        - Stories by survey respondents, (2 folders) (Box 17)
        - Stories collected from survey, (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Foreign news index
    - Event: patterns in U.S. coverage of specific events, 1990, (3 folders) (Box 18)
    - Medium: studies of types of medium and media structure, 1990, (3 folders) (Box 18)
    - Theory: studies of the nature of the media, 1990, (4 folders) (Box 19)
  - The Government/Press Connection: Press Officers and Their Offices
    - Daily notes
      - Food and Drug Administration, 1981-1983 (Box 19)
      - Pentagon, 1982 (Box 19)
      - State Department, 1982, (2 folders) (Box 20)
      - Transportation Department, 1982 (Box 20)
      - White House, 1982 (Box 20)
    - Drafts and chapter material
      - Part 1, 1981-1982, (4 folders) (Box 20)
      - Part 2, 1981-1982, (4 folders) (Box 21)
  - International News & Foreign Correspondents
    - Articles, 1964-1992 (Box 21)
    - Footnotes
      - Chapter One: Introduction, 1996 (Box 21)
      - Chapter Two: How Much is Not Enough?, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 22)
      - Chapter Three: Status Report, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Chapter Four: Who Gets Covered?, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Chapter Five: Men, Women, Children, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 22)
      - Chapter Six: What Gets Covered?, 1996, (1 folder) (Box 22)
      - Chapter Six: What Gets Covered?, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 23)
      - Chapter Seven: Pecking Order, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 23)
      - Chapter Eight: Technology, 1996 (Box 23)
      - Chapter Nine: Marginals, 1996 (Box 23)
      - Chapter Ten: Languages, 1996 (Box 23)
      - Chapter Twelve: Constructive Criticism, 1996, (3 folders) (Box 24)
      - Chapter Thirteen: Leaving, 1996 (Box 24)
    - Trends in technology, 1992 (Box 24)
    - United States Information Service, 1992 (Box 24)
  - Lead stories in newspapers, frequencies, and trends, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Lead stories in newspapers, frequencies, and trends, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Live From Capitol Hill!: Studies of Congress and the Media
    - Author's note, 1988-1990 (Box 25)
    - Demographics, 1974-1989 (Box 25)
    - "How Many Press Secretaries Does It Take to Change a Lightbulb?", 1984, (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - "In the Gallery," 1971-1990, (3 folders) (Box 26)
    - Op-ed pages, 1984-1989 (Box 26)
    - Press releases, 1984-1989, (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - Press secretary materials, 1981-1991 (Box 26)
    - Television articles, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - Verification, 1989, (3 folders) (Box 27)
  - Local television news
    - Impact of television news on 1990 election, 1990 (Box 27)
    - Interviews with directors and regional Washington, D.C. reporters, 1985-1989, (4 folders) (Box 28)
    - Newscasts by rank, 1987, (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - Survey, 1987, (2 folders) (Box 29)
  - Network news presidential campaign coverage, 2000 (Box 29)
  - Persian Gulf War
    - Cable News Network (CNN) coverage, 1994, (4 folders) (Box 29)
    - Chronological material, 1990-1991, (3 folders) (Box 30)
  - Presidential staffing papers, 1963-1977, (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - Press secretaries
    - United States House of Representatives
      - Biographies, 1988-1990 (Box 30)
      - Surveys, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 31)
      - Surveys and SPSS data, 1988-1990, (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - United States Senate
      - Biographies and news articles, 1983-1987, (3 folders) (Box 31)
      - Interviews, 1990 (Box 32)
      - Surveys, 1988-1990, (3 folders) (Box 32)
  - Reporter interviews
    - Abernethy, Bob, 1978, 1999-2000, 2007 (Box 32)
    - Abramson, Rudy, 1978, 2007-2008 (Box 32)
    - Adams, James, 1978, 2007 (Box 32)
    - Adams, James M., 1978, 2007 (Box 32)
    - Adams, Robert, 1978 (Box 32)
    - Albright, Joseph, 1978, 2007 (Box 32)
    - Aldrich, Charles, 1978, 2007-2009 (Box 32)
    - Aldrich, Nancy, 1978, 2007 (Box 32)
    - Alexander, Andrew, 1978, 2006 See also Container 59, See also mss83739_163_028, See also mss83739_163_029, and See also mss83739_163_027 (Box 32)
    - Allen, Ira, 1978, 2006-2007 (Box 32)
    - Alwood, Edward, 1978, 2006-2009 (Box 32)
    - Anderson, Helen, 1978 (Box 33)
    - Anderson, Jim, 1978, 2002, 2011 (Box 33)
    - Antevil, Jeffrey, 1978, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Arehart-Treichel, Joan, 1978, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Arieff, Irwin B., 1978, 2009 (Box 33)
    - Arvidson, Cheryl, 1978, 2006 (Box 33)
    - Aug, Stephen, 1978, 2000, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Averill, John, 1978, 1984 (Box 33)
    - Bacon, Donald C., 1978, 2004-2007 (Box 33)
    - Bailey, Becky, 1978, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Bailey, Gil, 1978, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Bain, Jackson, 1978, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Bandy, Lee, 1978, 1987-1991, 2005-2006 (Box 33)
    - Barbieri, Anthony, 1978, 2005-2007 (Box 33)
    - Barnett, David, 1978, 2008 (Box 33)
    - Baron, Stephen M., 1978, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Barton, John, 1978, 2009 (Box 33)
    - Barton, Sally Reynolds, 1978 (Box 33)
    - Bascom, Jon, 1978, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Battey, Phil, 1978, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Baulch, Jerry, 1978, 1985 (Box 33)
    - Bazell, Robert, 1978, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Beecher, William, 1978, 2005-2007 (Box 33)
    - Behr, Edward A., 1978, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Bell, Steve, 1978, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Benedict, Howard, 1978, 2005-2009 (Box 33)
    - Benjamin, Stan, 1978, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Berkowitz, Bob, 1978, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Berlow, Alan, 1978, 2008 (Box 33)
    - Bernstein, Jonathan L., 1978, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Bethell, Tom, 1978, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Betts, Roy, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Blake, Michael H., Jr., 1978, 2008 (Box 33)
    - Blanchard, Allan E., 1978 (Box 34)
    - Blatt, Dan, 1978, 2006 (Box 34)
    - Blount, Charlotte, 1978 (Box 34)
    - Bode, Roy E., 1978, 2006-2007 (Box 34)
    - Bolbach, Cynthia, 1978, 2005-2012 (Box 34)
    - Bonafede, Dom, 1978, 2008 (Box 34)
    - Bonner, Christopher, 1978, 2006 (Box 34)
    - Bowne, Thomas M., 1978 (Box 34)
    - Boyce, Richard, 1978, 2000 (Box 34)
    - Braaten, Susan Fogg, 1978, 2007 (Box 37)
    - Bradee, Richard, 1978, 1989, 2009 (Box 34)
    - Bradsher, Henry S., 1978, 2009 (Box 34)
    - Brazaitis, Tom, 1978, 2005-2008 (Box 34)
    - Brown, Warren, 1978, 2006-2011 (Box 34)
    - Buchanan, Christopher, 1978, 2008 (Box 34)
    - Burkhardt, Robert, 1978, 1999 (Box 34)
    - Burns, Kathleen M., 1978, 2006-2011 (Box 34)
    - Burns, Robert, 1978, 2007 See also Container 60 (Box 34)
    - Burt, Richard R., 1978, 2006-2007 See also mss83739_163_031 (Box 34)
    - Byrd, Lee, 1978, 2004 (Box 34)
    - Cameron, Juan M., 1978, 2009 (Box 34)
    - Campbell, Don, 1978, 1987, 2007 (Box 34)
    - Camper, Diane, 1978, 2009 (Box 34)
    - Canan, James W., 1978, 2007 (Box 34)
    - Carelli, Richard, 1978, 2007 (Box 34)
    - Carlson, Herbert P., 1978, 2008 (Box 34)
    - Cary, James, 1978, 2007 (Box 34)
    - Cawthorne, David, 1978, 1998, 2008 (Box 34)
    - Cazalas, Robert P., 1978, 2007-2010 (Box 34)
    - Chamberlayne, Pye, 1978, 2006 (Box 34)
    - Choyke, Bill, 1978, 2006 (Box 34)
    - Christy, Jeffrey, 1978 (Box 34)
    - Cimons, Marlene, 1978, 2006-2011 (Box 34)
    - Claiborne, William, 1978, 2007-2011 (Box 34)
    - Clayton, William, 1978 (Box 34)
    - Clymer, Adam, 1977-1978, 2005-2010 (Box 34)
    - Coates, Jim, 1978, 2006-2007 (Box 35)
    - Cohen, Richard E., 1978, 2006 (Box 35)
    - Cohn, Victor, 1978, 2000 (Box 35)
    - Cole, Benjamin, 1978, 1987. 2002-2008 (Box 35)
    - Cole, Martha, 1978, 1986 (Box 35)
    - Comarow, Avery, 1978, 2009 (Box 35)
    - Compton, Ann, 1978, 2006 (Box 35)
    - Conderacci, Greg, 1978, 2005-2007 (Box 35)
    - Conlon, Mike, 1978, 2007 (Box 35)
    - Connell, Christopher, 2003-2006 (Box 35)
    - Connolly, Mike, 1978, 1986, 2006 (Box 35)
    - Conover, Lynn, 1978 (Box 35)
    - Conte, Christopher Allan, 1978, 2006-2007 (Box 35)
    - Conway, William, 1978 (Box 35)
    - Cook, Rhodes, 1978, 2006 (Box 35)
    - Cormier, Frank, 1978, 1994 (Box 35)
    - Cowan, Edward, 2004-2011 (Box 35)
    - Cox, Merrilee, 1978, 2005-2009 (Box 35)
    - Crawford-Mason, Clare, 1978, 2005-2007 (Box 35)
    - Crock, Stan, 1978, 2009 (Box 35)
    - Crowley, Mary, 1978, 2007 (Box 35)
    - Cruickshank, Paula Lazor, 1978, 2007 (Box 35)
    - Cullen, Robert, 1978, 2007 (Box 35)
    - Cunningham, Robert, 1978, 2007 (Box 35)
    - Curley, John, 1978, 2009 (Box 35)
    - Dalecki, Ken, 1978, 2007 (Box 35)
    - Dancy, John, 1978, 2002-2007 (Box 35)
    - Daniloff, Nicholas, 1978, 2007-2008 (Box 35)
    - Davey, Charles H., 1999 (Box 35)
    - Dawson, Russell, 1978, 2007-2009 (Box 35)
    - Dear, David, 1978, 2007 (Box 35)
    - Degler, Stanley E., 1978, 2007-2008 (Box 35)
    - Delaney, William, 1978, 1991 (Box 35)
    - DeLong, Edward K., 1978, 2006 (Box 35)
    - Denniston, Lyle W., 1978, 2005-2012 (Box 35)
    - Deschenes, Michele, 1978 (Box 35)
    - Devroy, Ann, 1978, 2004-2008 (Box 36)
    - Dewar, Helen, 1978, 2006 (Box 36)
    - DeWitt, Karen, 1978, 2005-2006 (Box 36)
    - Dickenson, James R., 1978, 2007 (Box 36)
    - Dimond, Thomas, 1978 (Box 36)
    - Dininny, Paulette, 1978, 2007 (Box 36)
    - Dobrzynski, Judith H., 1978, 2006-2007 (Box 36)
    - Dombrowski, Cathy, 1978, 2009 (Box 36)
    - Donaldson, Sam, 1978, 2009 (Box 36)
    - Doyle, James, 1978, 2006-2009 (Box 36)
    - Duke, Robert, 1978, 2001 (Box 36)
    - Dunsmore, Barrie, 1978, 2002-2007 (Box 36)
    - Duvall, Jed, 1978, 2008 (Box 36)
    - Eagle, Jacqueline E., 1978, 2011 (Box 36)
    - Earle, G., 1978 (Box 36)
    - Eastham, Thomas, 1978, 2005, 2013 (Box 36)
    - Eaton, William J., 1978, 2005-2008 (Box 36)
    - Eberhart, Jonathan, 1978, 2003 (Box 36)
    - Eberle, Jim, 1978, 2007 (Box 36)
    - Edwards, Tom, 1978 (Box 36)
    - Egerstrom, Lee, 1978, 2007 (Box 36)
    - Elsasser, Glen, 1978, 2007-2011 (Box 36)
    - Emory, Alan, 1978, 2000, 2008 (Box 36)
    - Epstein, Aaron, 1978, 2010-2011 (Box 36)
    - Eskey, Ken, 1978, 2006 (Box 36)
    - Everett, Glenn D., 1978, 1996 (Box 36)
    - Falk, Carol, 1978, 2007 (Box 36)
    - Fanning, Patricia, 1978, 2007-2010 (Box 36)
    - Farmer, Don, 1978, 2006-2011 (Box 36)
    - Farney, Dennis, 1978, 2006-2007 (Box 36)
    - Fassberg, Benjamin, 1977 (Box 37)
    - Fattibene, Jim, 1978, 1994, 2006 (Box 37)
    - Feinsilber, Mike, 1978, 2007 (Box 37)
    - Fentress, Simmons, 1978-1986, 2008 (Box 37)
    - Fialka, John J., 1978, 2006-2008 See also mss83739_163_004 (Box 37)
    - Fiedler, Tom, 1978, 2004-2010 (Box 37)
    - Flanagan, Mike, 1978 (Box 37)
    - Fogarty, John, 1978, 2010 (Box 37)
    - Foster, James, 1978 (Box 37)
    - Foty, Tom, 1978, 2008 (Box 37)
    - Fox, Larry, 1978, 2007, 2013 (Box 37)
    - Free, James, 1978, 1996 (Box 37)
    - Friedman, Saul, 1978, 2008 (Box 37)
    - Fuller, Jack, 1978, 2003-2016 (Box 37)
    - Garcia, David, 1978, 2007 (Box 37)
    - Gay, Lance, 1978, 2006 (Box 37)
    - Gedda, George, 1978, 2009 (Box 37)
    - Gerstenzang, James, 1978, 2009 (Box 37)
    - Gest, Kathryn, 1978, 2008-2009 (Box 37)
    - Gest, Ted, 1978, 2008 See also Container 45 and See also mss83739_163_020 (Box 37)
    - Gettlin, Robert, 1978, 2006 (Box 37)
    - Gill, Kathleen D., 1978, 1996-1997 (Box 37)
    - Gilmore, Daniel, 1978, 1988 (Box 37)
    - Glass, Andrew J., 1978, 1997-2010 See also mss83739_163_027 (Box 37)
    - Goldenberg, Gene, 1978, 2010 (Box 37)
    - Gordon, Gregory, 1978, 2005-2009 (Box 37)
    - Gorey, Hays, 1978, 2009 (Box 38)
    - Goshko, John, 1978, 1999, 2001, 2009 (Box 38)
    - Graham, Fred P., 1978, 2008 See also mss83739_163_044 (Box 38)
    - Greenberger, Robert, 1978, 2007 (Box 38)
    - Gregory, Bettina, 1978, 2003 (Box 38)
    - Greve, Frank, 1978, 2006 (Box 38)
    - Guillory, Ferrel, 1978, 2006 (Box 38)
    - Gwertzman, Bernard M., 1978, 2002-2006 (Box 38)
    - Haberek, Judy, 1978, 2007 (Box 38)
    - Hall, Wilson, 1978, 1991, 2008 (Box 38)
    - Halloran, Richard, 1978, 2002-2007 (Box 38)
    - Hanna, Sam, 1978 (Box 38)
    - Hannifin, Jerry, 1978, 1995, 2008-2010 (Box 38)
    - Harris, Emily, 1978 (Box 38)
    - Hartge, John, 1978, 2006-2008 (Box 38)
    - Hedges, Roger, 1978, 2007 (Box 38)
    - Heinl, Robert Debs, 1978-1979 (Box 38)
    - Heller, Jean, 1978, 2007 (Box 38)
    - Henck, Fred W., 1978, 1988, 2008 (Box 38)
    - Herman, George, 1978, 2005 (Box 38)
    - Herzog, James, 1978, 1982 (Box 38)
    - Hess, David, 1978, 2006 (Box 38)
    - Hickling, Lee, 1978 (Box 38)
    - Hickman, Bill, 1978, 1988, 2002, 2008-2010 (Box 38)
    - Hildreth, James, 1978 (Box 38)
    - Hiner, Louis C., Jr., 1978, 1987, 2008 (Box 38)
    - Hoagland, Jim, 1978 (Box 38)
    - Holliman, John, 1978, 1998, 2008 (Box 38)
    - Holmes, Peter, 1978, 2007 (Box 38)
    - Hoover, Don, 1978 (Box 38)
    - Hornig, Roberta, 1978-1981, 2007 (Box 38)